bollyupdates.com 2012-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Bollywood Updates

[Home](http://www.bollyupdates.com/ "Go to Home.") > Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site www.bollyupdates.com . The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter (powered by Feedburner), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user.

www.bollyupdates.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense (including their [partners](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149&ctx=sibling)), Chitika and Adbrite etc. . Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: admin [at] bollyupdates.com

All images and text copyright to their owners and used under the fair use copyright law, section 107. All images and text are thought to be public domain and found through various free sources on the internet and publications. **Please contact us with any legal problems and we’ll be happy to remove any thing in breach.**

“Sec. 107. – Limitations on exclusive rights: Fair use

“Notwithstanding the provisions of sections 106 and 106A, the fair use of a copyrighted work, including such use by reproduction in copies or phonorecords or by any other means specified by that section, for purposes such as criticism, comment, news reporting, teaching (including multiple copies for classroom use), scholarship, or research, is not an infringement of copyright.”
